Sandra Maksimovic

https://github.com/sanmaksim

Summary

Qualified IT professional with experience in software development and systems administration. Demonstrated ability in professional communication, collaboration, problem solving, troubleshooting, data analysis, performance optimisation, documentation and project management. Highly adaptable self-starter and creative thinker; accustomed to constantly evolving technology. Home lab enthusiast with a keen interest in open-source software, hardware, and user education.

Education

Swinburne University of Technology

2005 - 2008

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science and Software Engineering) / Bachelor of Multimedia (Games and Interactivity)

Skills

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, Java, C#, C++, Bash, Python, Perl, PowerShell, Git, Docker, Ansible, Nginx, Apache, CI/CD, MySQL, PostgreSQL, TCP/IP, AD/Entra ID, VMware, Storage, Security, Networking, Windows, Linux, HPC

Experience

Career Transition

Software development self-study, projects and travel

April 2024 – Present

- Gameplays Video game manager/tracker web app with TS/React front-end and ASP.NET (C#) server API
- Guavanoid Pure JavaScript block-breaker game utilising the Canvas API

Murdoch Children's Research Institute

Senior Systems Administrator

Nov 2014 - Feb 2024

- Built and maintained the institute's High Performance Computing cluster (Meerkat)
- Deployed and configured a multitude of scientific open-source software and e-research platforms for HPC
- Automated Linux server deployment and patching via Ansible
- Managed the institute's server, storage and networking infrastructure
- Maintained internally hosted research-study web apps

Murdoch Children's Research Institute

Service Desk Technical Officer

May 2012 - Oct 2014

- Answered calls, performed troubleshooting, resolved user incidents
- Utilised configuration management tools such as SCCM and JAMF to deploy software and settings
- Automated various operational tasks using Batch Script, VBScript and PowerShell
- Managed the institute's fleet of Windows, Mac and Linux desktop computers

Sunbury College

IT Technician

Jan 2012 – April 2012

- Maintained school computers, A/V equipment, back-end infrastructure
- Performed troubleshooting, resolved classroom computer issues

Blue Tongue Entertainment

Level Designer

Jan 2009 – Aug 2011

- Brainstormed and prototyped level ideas for upcoming games, incorporating feedback from weekly peer reviews
- Designed and implemented several levels for a game called 'de Blob 2' using the in-house level editor
- Engaged in extensive play-testing and bug-fixing
- Mentored new starters and interns

Blue Tongue Entertainment

Quality Assurance / Level Design Intern

Jan 2008 – Dec 2008

- Performed various types of play-testing, logged bugs using in-house bug tracking software
- Submitted regular quality reports and feedback to the development team
- Designed a level using the in-house development tools and Nintendo Wii development kit

References